{
    "subject": "resource/Disco_2000_(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/subsequentWork",
    "object": "resource/Something_Changed",
    "human_readable": "Something Changed was a subsequent work of Disco 2000.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.895700991153717,
            "question": "Was Something Changed released before or after Disco 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8243709206581116,
            "question": "How might the sound of Something Changed differ from Disco 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7892418503761292,
            "question": "If someone enjoyed Disco 2000, would they probably also like Something Changed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7725875377655029,
            "question": "Do you know the artist who created Disco 2000 and Something Changed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7593048214912415,
            "question": "What was the title of the work that followed Disco 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.06095714867115021,
            "question": "What genre of music is likely associated with these titles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04969580098986626,
            "question": "What kind of impact do you think these musical works have had on listeners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04814009368419647,
            "question": "What might be some common themes explored in these musical works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03418104723095894,
            "question": "Are there any other musical works by this artist that you are familiar with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.025034762918949127,
            "question": "Can you name two musical works by this artist?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Something Changed was a subsequent work of Disco 2000.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1639_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other musical works by this artist that you are familiar with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1639_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some common themes explored in these musical works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1639_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of impact do you think these musical works have had on listeners?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1639_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1639_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Disco 2000\" is the third single from Pulp's album \"Different Class,\" and \"Something Changed\" is another top ten single from the same album, supporting the statement that \"Something Changed\" was a subsequent work of \"Disco 2000.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}